Finding Aid for the Herbert Charles Sanborn Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Correspondence - Incoming, Incoming correspondence of 4,326 letters, 235 post cards, and 70 telegrams. Alphabetically arranged, letters are typescript, holograph, and carbon copies. There are several circular and mimeographed. 1 Letters signed with initials only and with 1 name only are found at e
  - McKavney, John R. (12), NQV. 2, 1943, Nov. 10, 1943, Dec. 5, 1943, Jan. 12, 1944, Jan. 17, 1944, Feb. 14, 1944, Feb. 21, 1944, Mar. 25, 1944, Apr. 3, 1944, Apr. 28, 1944, May 17, 1944, Sept. 19, 1944 (Box 9)
  - McKee, Betty (2), May 29. 1959, Mar. 15, 1960 (Box 9)
  - McKee, Edward R. (1), Dec. 5, 1944 (Box 9)
  - McKee, Elizabeth (2), Aug. 3, 1944, Nov. 15, 1944 (Box 9)
  - McKenzie, Duncan H. (1), Mar. 29, 1950 (Box 9)
  - McKinney, Carole (1), Mar. 15, 1960 (Box 9)
  - McKinney, Harold F. (1), Nov. 13, 1959 (Box 9)
  - McMorrow, J.p. (2), July 15, 1946, July 24, 1946 (Box 9)
  - McMurray, Hatchery (1), (n.d.) (outgoing letter from sanborn included on this incoming letter) (Box 9)
  - McNaughtan, Thomas J. (1), Aug. 30, 1952 (Box 9)
  - McNeill, Robert H. (1), July 1954 (Box 9)
  - McQueen, Josephine (1), Jan. 3, 1955 (Box 9)
  - McReynolds, A.B. (1), Sept. 21, 1949 (Box 9)
  - McVey, Mrs. Wm. M. (1), Feb. 6, 1940 (Box 9)
  - Machle, Florence M. (3), May 28, 1935, June 11, 1935, (n.d.) (Box 9)
  - Machle, Willard F. (4), Nov. 1, 1935, Dec. 15, 1944, May 15, 1945, Sept. 26, 1950 (Box 9)
  - Macintosh, Douglas Clyde (1), Feb. 28, 1935 (Box 9)
  - Maddy, Cora Lee (1), June 18, 1934 (Box 9)
  - Madrazo, J.M. (1), Sept. 3, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Magee, Chester L, (1), Jan. 5, 1944 (Box 9)
  - Maguire, Russell (2), May 22, 1958, May 22, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Mahan, F.A. (1), Dec. 5, 1944 (Box 9)
  - Maisky, Dick (1), May 6, 1953 (Box 9)
  - Makin, D. (11), Mar. 11, 1943, Mar. 16, 1943, Mar. 22, 1943, Mar. 25, 1943, Apr. 8, 1943, Aug. 26, 1943, Dec. 3, 1943, Apr. 22, 1944, Feb. 13, 1945, Mar. 29, 1945, Aug. 18, 1949 (Box 9)
  - Malisoff, W.M. (1), May 15, 1939 (Box 9)
  - Malone, Roy (10), Mar. 14, 1944 (post card), Nov. 24, 1944, Dec. 4, 1944 Aug. 23, 1954, June 24, 1955, June 11, 1956, Aug. 6, 1957, May 19, 1959, Nov. 17, 1959, (nd.) (Box 9)
  - Mangold, Edith E. (5), Mar. 19, 1933, Aug. 12, 1934, Apr. 5, 1935, July 18, 1935, Dec. 21, 1938 (Box 9)
  - Mangrum, Betty Jean (1), Mar. 1, 1946 (Box 9)
  - Manion, Clarence (2), Dec. 22, 1955, Jan. 12, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Mankin, Philip (1), Dec. 19, 1944 (Box 9)
  - Mann, F. Allen (1), Jan. 14, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Mann, Leon S. (9), May 28, 1943, July 16, 1943, July 19, 1943, Aug. 20, 1943, Oct. 26, 1943, Dec. 17, 1943, Dec. 28, 1943, Jan. 2, 1945, Jan. 4, 1945 (Box 9)
  - Mann, W.M. (2), July 10, 1935, Feb. 10, 1946 (Box 9)
  - Manwaring, Charles J. (2), May 8, 1950, May 24, 1950 (Box 9)
  - Manzer, George E. (1), May 25, 1950 (Box 9)
  - Marcus, L.G. (4), Dec. 2, 1943, Dec. 9, 1943, Dec. 22, 1943, Nov. 16, 1944 (Box 9)
  - Marett, W.W. (1), Jan. 17, 1949 (Box 9)
  - Markham, Jesse W. (3), Dec. 6, 1952, Feb. 6, 1953, May 6, 1953 (Box 9)
  - Markley, Chester R. (1), Feb. 23, 1951 (Box 9)
  - Marot, G.E.P. (3), May 8, 1944, Nov. 4, 1944, Nov. 27, 1944 (Box 9)
  - Marquardt, E.H. (6), Dec. 31, 1936, Aug. 9, 1944, Sept. 27, 1945, Aug. 28, 1946, Dec. 30, 1946, Jan. 21, 1947 (Box 9)
  - Marsh, Daniel L. (3), Apr. 25, 1946, Aug. 23, 1950, Mar. 28, 1952 (Box 9)
  - Marti, Fritz (13), Nov. 8, 1935, Apr. 12, 1944, May 22, 1944, Feb. 12 1945, June, 1946, Feb. 18, 1947, Mar. 30, 1947, May 18, 1948 (post card), Feb. 13, 1950, Mar. 8, 195 (Sept. 15, 1950, May 16, 1953, (n.d.) (Box 9)
  - Martin, Bradford (1), June 6, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Martin, Edward (1), Sept. 8, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Martin, LLoyd (1), (n.d.) (Box 9)
  - Martin, Sam (2), Feb. 16, 1945, Mar. 27, 1945 (Box 9)
  - Martin, Whitney W. (6), Nov. 9, 1943, Feb. 15, 1944, Feb. 28, 1944, June 17, 1944, Dec. 31, 1950 (Box 9)
  - Martin, Mrs. Whitney W. (1), Apr. 3, 1944 (telegram) (Box 9)
  - Martina, J.G. (1), Feb. 10, 1944 (Box 9)
  - Martinoff, Alexander P. (51), Aug. 1, 1942, Sept. 25, 1944, Feb. 26, 1945, Mar. 2, 1945, Apr. 5, 1945, Apr. 16, 1945 (telegram), Apr. 27, 1945, May 1, 1945, May 31, 1945 July 9, 1945, July 16, 1945, Aug. 4, 1945, Aug. 20, 1945, Aug. 31, 1945; Sept. 17, 1945, Oct. 9, 1945, Oct. 24, 1945, Nov. 13, 1945, Nov. 15, 1945, Nov. 26, 1945, Dec. 3, 1945, Dec. 4, 1945, Jan. 19, 1946, Jan. 29, 1946, Jan. 31, 1946, Feb. 20, 1946, Mar. 12 1946, Apr. 15, 1946, May 9, 1946, June 20, 1946; July 10, 1946, July 18, 1946, Aug. 1946, Oct. 8, 194 Nov. 29, 1946, Dec. 6, 1946, Jan. 21, 1947 Feb. 3, 1947, Feb. 7, 1947, Feb. 17, 1947, Mar. 10, 1947, June 11, 1948, Mar. 1, 1949, Sept. 30, 1949, Nov. 14, 1949, Nov. 26, 1949; Jan. 30, 1950, Aug. 14, 1950, Aug. 16, 1950, Aug. 31 (?), (n.d.) (Box 9)
  - Marts, L.A. (1), Sept. 6, 1949 (Box 9)
  - Mason, Karl E. (2), June 19, 1943, July 3, 1943 (Box 9)
  - Masse, Aileen Billings (4), Jan. 5, 1947, Jan. 13, 1947, Jan. 21, 1947, Feb. 14, 1947 (Box 9)
  - Matowitz, George J. (1), Mar. 29, 1933 (Box 9)
  - Matsunoto, Tatuo (1), Dec. 5, 1949 (Box 9)
  - Matthaey, Fritz (1), Aug. 7, 1946 (Box 9)
  - Matthews, Jim P. (1), Sept. 8, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Matthews, Marcia C.J. (1), Dec. 8, 1955 (Box 9)
  - Matthews, Robert W. (2), Sept. 15, 1955 (post card), (n.d.) (Box 9)
  - Matthews, W.L. (1), Feb. 21, 1950 (Box 9)
  - Mayer, Dore F. (1), Feb. 10', 1942 (to Dr.Johnson) (Box 9)
  - Mayes, Lambeth (1), (n.d.) (Box 9)
  - Mayfield, G.R. (1), Oct. 25, 1945 (to Frank Pattie) (Box 9)
  - Maynard, caroline K. (1), Jan. 8, 1951 (Box 9)
  - Maynard, Roger (1), Sept. 4, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Mayo, R.A. (1), May 22, 1935 (Box 9)
  - Mayo, R.A. Jr. (1), Oct. 2, 1945 (Box 9)
  - Mehrer, Maria (1), May 16, 1944 (Box 9)
  - Mehrer, Mr. and Mrs. (1), Dec. 16, 1942 (Box 9)
  - Mehus, O. MyKing (1), Nov. 10, 1944 (Box 9)
  - Melton, Ronald A. (1), Jan. 25, 1946 (outgoing letter from sanborn included on this incoming letter) (Box 9)
  - Melzer, John Henry (28), Jan. 15, 1935, Feb. 15, 1935, Apr. 17, 1935, Apr. 27, 1935, May 19, 1935, July 4, 1935, Sept. 7, 1943, Feb. 15, 1944, Mar. 2, 1944, Apr. 19, 1944, July 27, 1944, July 29, 1944, Nov. 2, 1944; Jan. 12, 1945, Jan. 22, 1945, Feb. 6, 1945, Mar. 9, 1945, Nov. 13, 1946, Mar. 5, 1947, Nov. 25, 1948, May 24, 1949, Oct. 26, 1949, Nov. 24, 1949, Dec. 1, 1950, Nov. 25, 1951, May 20, 1954, Oct. 11, 1956, (n.d.) (Box 10)
  - Melzer, John and Dorothy (1), Dec. 19, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Menjou, Adolphe (2), Mar. 15, 1957, (n.d.) (Box 10)
  - Menninger, Karl F. (1), May 29, 1929 (Box 10)
  - Mercado, Lucy (1), Mar. 18, 1959 (Box 10)
  - Merritt, Memory T. (1), Jan. 29, 1953 (Box 10)
  - Mersereau, Robert (1), May 7, 1956 (Box 10)
  - Meyer, Enno (1), June 26, 1944, Jan. 27, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Meyer, Gerry (32), Jan. 5, 1950, Jan. 27, 1950, Jan. 28, 1950 (post card), Feb. 5, 1950 (telegram), Feb. 9, 1950, Feb. 11, 1950, Mar. 17, 1950, Apr. 20, 1950, Apr. 21, 1950, June 22, 1950, Aug. 24, 1950, Oct. 22, 1950; Nov. 7, 1950, Nov. 22, 1950, Dec. 7, 1950, June 26, 1951, July 6, 1951, Aug. 22, 1951, Oct. 2, 1951 (post card), Oct. 17, 1951, Dec. 3, 1951, Jan. 15, 1952, Jan. 21, 1952, Feb. 5, 1952, May 23, 1952, Sept. 15, 1952, Sept. 23, 1952; Oct. 28, 1952, Oct. 29, 1952 (telegram), Mar. 12, 1953, Feb. 1, 1959 (Box 10)
  - Meyer, Gus H. (2), Aug. 22, 1951, Oct. 10, 1951 (telegram) (Box 10)
  - Meyer, Gus and Gerry (1), Dec. 19, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Meyer, Marie B. (1), June 6, 1944 (Box 10)
  - Meyer, Max F. (4), Oct. 8, 1948 (post card), Oct. 22, 1948 (post card), Nov. 5, 1948, (n.d.) (Box 10)
  - Meyers, Robert J. (1), Jan. 6, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Meyer-Neuhauser, E. (1), Sept. 1, 1953 (Box 10)
  - Milbank, samuel (3), July 3, 1934, Jan. 22, 1935?, Feb. 1, 1935? (Box 10)
  - Miles, Walter R. (1), July 9, 1940 (Box 10)
  - Miller, Albert B. Jr. (1), Feb. 23, 1953 (Box 10)
  - Miller, B.M. "Red" (1), Aug. 29, 1955 (Box 10)
  - Miller, Harry (1), 1945 (Box 10)
  - Miller, Mrs. Hilliard Jr. (1), Oct. 1, 1947 (Box 10)
  - Miller, Horace Sherman (1), (n.d.) (Box 10)
  - Miller, Manuel s. and Lucille s. (3), Sept. 2, 1955 (to Austin H. Kerin), Nov. 24, 1955 (to Winifred Overholser), Dec. 10, 1955 (Box 10)
  - Milner, Lucille B. (1), June 7, 1935 (Box 10)
  - Mims, Edwin (2), Aug. 20, 1922, Dec. 12, 1945 (Box 10)
  - Miner, J.B. (2), Apr. 26, 1924, Aug. 20, 1930 (Box 10)
  - Minor, Louise B. (3), Feb. 8, 1955, Mar. 1, 1956, Mar. 1, 1956 (Box 10)
  - Minor, Robert w. (1), Aug. 22, 1952 (Box 10)
  - Mitchell, Roy L. (3), July 28, 1952 (to John s. Battle), July 29, 1952 (to Adlai Stevenson), Aug. 2, 1952 (Box 10)
  - Modern Dogs (1), Feb. 20, 1947 (post card) (Box 10)
  - Molyneaux, Lambert (3), Mar. 2, 1950 (telegram,), Mar. 7, 1950, Mar. 14, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Monroe, Helen (10), June 3, 1944, July 4, 1944, Dec. 27, 1944, Mar. 18, 1947, Nov. 15, 1949, Nov. 16, 1949 (to Mary Cobb), Nov. 26, 1949, Jan. 5, 1950, June 2, 1950, (n.d.) (Box 10)
  - Montgomery, Robert H. (1), Nov. 8, 1955 (Box 10)
  - Moody, Barbara and Bob (1), Dec. 24, 1952 (Box 10)
  - Moody, Robert E. (4), Jan. 6, 1955, Jan. 6, 1955 (to Frank W. Kimball), Aug.18, 1955, Oct. 25, 1955 (Box 10)
  - Moore, Annie (1), Sept. 18, 1945 (Box 10)
  - Moore, John w. (1), Mar. 6, 1956 (Box 10)
  - Moore, Joseph E. (3), June 3, 1954, Mar. 22, 1955, (n.d.) (Box 10)
  - Moore, Merrill (4), Thanksgiving 1944, November 1944, 1944 (to Commanding Officer), Aug. 31, 1949 (Box 10)
  - Moore, Pugh (2), Sept. 25, 1952, Oct. 22, 1952 (Box 10)
  - Moore, Willis (1), Apr. 9, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Morenus, Richard T. (3), Apr. 25, 1952, Apr. 20, 1954, Jan. 6, 1957 (Box 10)
  - Morford, Theodore (1), Dec. 18, 1955 (Box 10)
  - Morgan, Theodore (1), Dec. 18, 1955 (Box 10)
  - Morgan, Hugh J. (1), Jan. 12, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Marple, Dan D. (1), Oct. 16, 1957 (Box 10)
  - Morris, Albert (1), Sept. 10, 1954 (to Frank W. Kimball) (Box 10)
  - Morris, Evelyn G. (3), June 6, 1946, July 4, 1946, Nov. 20, 1946 (Box 10)
  - Morris, James R. (1), May 16, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Morris, Jane W. (1), May 31, 1954 (Box 10)
  - Morrison, deLesseps S. (1), Jan. 14, 1959 (Box 10)
  - Morrison, Mr. and Mrs. White Hall (1), Oct. 5, 1954 (Box 10)
  - Morriss, Irene (1), Jan. 8, 1953 (Box 10)
  - Morrissey, Ralph G. (3), June 13, 1944 (post card), Feb. 15, 1945 (post card), Mar. 28, 1945 (post card) (Box 10)
  - Morse, Josiah (7), Apr. 14, 1924, Apr. 18, 1926, Nov. 16, 1926, Apr. 25, 1927, Feb. 10, 1928, July 29, 1936, Feb. 7, 1943 (Box 10)
  - Morse, Rose (1), Nov. 18, 1949 (Box 10)
  - Moseley, George Van Horn (2), Jan. 28, 1957, May 28, 1959 (Box 10)
  - Mosig, Robert (1), Jan. 31, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Moss, Charles (9), Mar. 30, 1950, Feb. 27, 1951, Mar. 30, 1953, Apr. 20, 1953, May 18, 1954, Aug. 24, 1954, June 16, 1955, Apr. 16, 1956, Aug. 20, 1957 (Box 10)
  - Moss, W.D. (1), Feb. 11, 1946 (Box 10)
  - Motlow, Jeanie Garth (2), Mar. 3, 1944, Mar. 28, 1944 (Box 10)
  - Mottern, R.W. (1), May 28, 1946 (post card) (Box 10)
  - Moulton, F.R. (1), Oct. 2, 1944 (Box 10)
  - Mount, Katrinka Suydam (1), (n.d.) (Box 10)
  - Mowrer, O.H. (1), Feb. 25, 1933 (Box 10)
  - Muncy, L.L. (1), Nov. 1, 1957 (Box 10)
  - Mundt, Karl E. (1), Sept. 10, 1954 (Box 10)
  - Mune, Norman (1), Mar. 13,1950 (post card) (Box 10)
  - Munro, Thomas (1), Jan. 26, 1959 (post card) (Box 10)
  - Murchison, Carl (5), Dec. 4, 1950, Dec. 26, 1950, Feb. 26, 1951, July 3, 1954, (n.d.) (Box 10)
  - Murphy, Arthur E. (1), May 16, 1935 (Box 10)
  - Murray, Albert A. (2), May 22,1952, (n.d.) (Box 10)
  - Murray, Beckey (1), Aug. 29, 1952 (Box 10)
  - Murrey, Harry P. Jr. (1), June 26, 1956 (Box 10)
  - Musser, Karl B. (1), Feb. 26, 1945 (Box 10)
  - Nafe, John P. (4), Mar. 12, 1950 (post card), May 21, 1954, Apr. 6, 1956, May 11, 1956 (Box 10)
  - Nahm, Milton c. (1), Feb. 1, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Nance, James E. (1), May 23, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Nardo, A.J. (1), (n.d.) (Box 10)
  - Nashville Civic Music Assn (1), (n.d.) (Box 10)
  - Nashville Gun Club (2), Apr. 6, 1944 (post card), Apr. 12, 1944 (Box 10)
  - Nashville Kennel Club (1), May 21, 1945 (post card) (Box 10)
  - National Renaissance Party (1), June 1, 1955 (Box 10)
  - Naylor, Pete (4), Mar. 13, 1950, Apr. 18, 1950, Oct. 23, 1951, July 23, 1955 (Box 10)
  - Needham, P. Henry (1), July 8, 1957 (Box 10)
  - Negley, Glenn (1), Feb. 14, 1952 (Box 10)
  - Neil, A.B. (2), Sept. 25, 1951, July 15, 1954 (Box 10)
  - Nelson, Carol L. (2), Apr. 16, 1947, Apr. 30, 1947 (Box 10)
  - Nesbitt, Gordon A. (102), May 13, 1943 (post card), Oct. 19, 1943, Feb. 11, 1944, Mar. 8, 1944, Mar. 19, 1944, Apr. 2, 1944, Apr. 16, 1944, May 15, 1944, June 18, 1944, July 4, 1944, July 8, 1944, July 29, 1944, Aug. 17, 1944, Sept. 26, 1944 (to Mrs. Cobb); Oct. 2, 1944 (to Mrs. Cobb), Oct. 3, 1944, Oct. 15, 1944, Nov. 13, 19 Nov. 26, 1944, Dec. 4, 1944, Dec. 25, 1944, Jan. 14, 1945 (post card), Jan. 25, 1945, Jan. 27, 1945 (telegram), Feb. 4, 1945, Feb. 4, 1945 (telegram), Feb. 1 1945; Mar. 2, 1945, Mar. 29, 1945, Apr. 10, 1945, May 2, 1945, May 21, 1945, July 2, 1945, July 9, 194 July 28, 1945, Sept. 11, 1945, Sept. 23, 1945, Sept. 30, 1945, Oct. 2, 1945, Oct. 8, 1945, Oct. 15, 1945, (telegram); Nov. 4, 1945, Nov. 8, 1945 (telegram), Nov. 17, 1945, July 21, 1946, Jan. 18, 1948, Mar. 13, 1948, Oct. 25, 1948, June 30, 1949, July 6, 1949; Aug. 18, 1949, Sept. 14, 1949, Sept. 20, 194 Sept. 21, 1949, Sept. 25, 1949, Oct. 21, 1949, Nov. 15, 1949, Dec. 18, 1949; Jan. 31, 1950, Mar. 12, 1950 Apr. 26, 1950, May 3, 1950, May 8, 1950, May 15, 1950, June 1, 1950, June 25, 1950, July 20, 1950, Aug. 20, 1950; Sept. 4, 1950, Sept. 21, 1950, oct. 11 1950, Oct. 16, 1950, Jan. 10, 1951, Feb. 14, 1951, Feb 19, 1951; Apr. 4, 1951, Apr. 16, 1951, May 10, 1951, July 17, 1951, July 21, 1951, Aug. 13, 1951, Oct. 10, 1951, Nov. 6, 1951, Nov. 23, 1951, Jan. 30, 1952, Apr. 9, 1952, Apr. 29, 1952, June 23, 1952, Sept. 16, 1952, Oct. 20, 1952, Nov. 17, 1952; Jan. 7, 1953, Mar. 1, 1953, Mar. 16, 1953, June 16, 1953, Nov. 16, 1953, July 22, 1954, Aug. 23, 1954, Sept. 2, 1954, Apr. 6, 1955, June 30, 1955, July 21, 1960 (Box 10, Box 11)
  - Nesbitt, Betty Mae and Gordon (4), Dec. 17, 1944, Apr. 4, 1950, Dec. 3, 1950, July 10, 1965 (Box 11)
  - Neuman, Henry (1), Aug. 25, 1956 (Box 11)
  - Nevans, H.B. (1), Apr. 11, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Nevans, Mrs. H.B. (1), July 13, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Newbold, H.L. (2), June 6, 1949 (post card), (n.d.) (Box 11)
  - Newbold, Susan (2), Aug. 7, 1949 (post card), (n.d.) (Box 11)
  - Newbold, Hank and Susan (1), Dec. 19, 1949 (Box 11)
  - Newman, Harold (1), Nov. 27, 1937 (Box 11)
  - Nice, Margaret M. (1), Nov. 17, 1934 (post card) (Box 11)
  - Nicely, Glen (1), July 16, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Nichols, Joe D. (1), Feb. 26, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Nichols, Mary (2), Apr. 20, 1944, Oct. 18, 1944 (Box 11)
  - Nitsche, J.L. (1), Jan. 7, 1946 (Box 11)
  - Nixon, C.William (1), Mar. 15, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Nobbe, E.H. (1), June 28, 1946 (Box 11)
  - Noble, Eugene A. (1), Apr. 26, 1926 (Box 11)
  - Noel, Hayes (1), Apr. 7, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Noel, Oscar F. (1), June 7, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Norris, Dwight W. (1), Feb. 28, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Norvell, W.E., Jr. (1), Oct. 26, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Nuckols, Hrs. J. Cecil Jr. (1), Oct. 11, 1943 (Box 11)
  - Nuffer, O.G. (1), Feb. 17, 1946 (Box 11)
  - Nunnelley, H.Martin (1), Oct. 14, 1959 (Box 11)
  - Nutting, H.C. (1), Sept. 26, 1927 (Box 11)
  - Nye, John H. (1), Mar. 27, 1947 (Box 11)
  - O'Conner, M. (1), June 16, 1944 (Box 11)
  - O'Conner, William J. (1), (n. 4.) (Box 11)
  - O'Donohue, Renie H. (5), June 21, 1945, July 23, 1945, Aug. 11, 1945, Sept. 5, 1945, Nov. 20, 1945 (Box 11)
  - O'Malley, Edward J. (5), Dec. 23, 1950 (post card), Jan. 6, 1951 (post card), Mar. 8, 1951 (post card), Aug. 28, 1952 (post card), Sept. 6, 1952 (post card) (Box 11)
  - O'Neall, Johns. (7), July 17, 1951, Aug. 6, 1951, May 12, 1952, Hay 14, 1952 (to J.S. Williams), May 17, 1952, Hay 19, 1952, (n.d.) (Box 11)
  - Odegaard, Charles E. (1), (n.d.) (Box 11)
  - Ogden, C.K. (1), Dec. 17 (Box 11)
  - Ogden, R.M. (2), Oct. 26, 1925, July 28, 1948 (Box 11)
  - Oliphant, Willard (1), Mar. 25, 1950 (post card) (Box 11)
  - Oliver, Revilo Pendleton (2), Oct. 4, 1959 1 Jan. 18, 1961 (Box 11)
  - Oliver, William Henry (2), Dec. 2, 1952 (to A.P.Ottarson, Jr.), Jan. 26, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Omberg, Arthur (2), Nov. 17, 1952 (post card), Mar. 12, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Omberg, Helen (1), Nov. 7, 1952 (Box 11)
  - Opper, F.H. (1), Jan. 17, 1936 (Box 11)
  - Opperman, Carl W. (1), Apr. 4, 1935 (to Mr.Horswell) (Box 11)
  - Orne, Stanley (2), Jan. 22, 1960, Feb. 11, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Orr, Mrs.L. (1), July 2, 1951 (Box 11)
  - Ortmann, Mrs.Paul H. (5), Dec. 18, 1944, Mar. 2, 1950, Mar. 3, 1950 (post card), Jan. 2, 1951, May 17, 1951 (Box 11)
  - Osborn, Jesse (1), July 7, 1954 (to Dr.Brown) (Box 11)
  - Osuna, Andres (2), May 14, 1945, Mar. 31, 1952 (Box 11)
  - Otting, Eve (1), Nov. 14, 1945 (Box 11)
  - Overall, Nadine Webb (1), Mar. 15, 1942 (Box 11)
  - Overcash, Mrs. E.D. (1), July 6, 1951 (Box 11)
  - Overcash, E.D. (1), July 19, 1951 (telegram) (Box 11)
  - Owsley, FrankL. (3), Mar. 11, 1950, June 21, 1952, Dec. 15, 1953 (Box 11)
  - Ozier, John R. (1), June 8, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Pace, Carrie M. (1), Mar. 10, 1942 (Box 11)
  - Paddock, Mrs. Ford (1), Mar. 31, 1953 (Box 11)
  - Palmer, J.S. (1), Jan. 15, 1945 (post card) (Box 11)
  - Parker, F.S. (1), Jan. 2, 1944 (Box 11)
  - Parker, Frances (1), Nov. 4, 1957 (Box 11)
  - Parker, Marjorie (1), July 27, 1943 (poet card) (Box 11)
  - Parkinson, B.H.Jr. (1), Mar. 10, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Parks, T.E. (1), Mar. 19, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Parka, Mrs.T.E. (1), Mar. 24, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Parks, WarrenS. (1), Apr. 14, 1932 (Box 11)
  - Parsley, Gertrude Morton (2), May 26, 1958, (n.d.) (Box 11)
  - Passey, George E. (1), Oct. 1950 (post card) (Box 11)
  - Paschal, F.C. (4), Feb. 26, 1935, Apr. 1, 1935, Apr. 23, 1935, Oct. 4, 1935 (Box 11)
  - Patterson, B.K. (1), Dec. 21, 1954 (to Mrs.L.L.Minor) (Box 11)
  - Patterson, Robert B. (1), June 29, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Pattie, Frank A. (28), July 10, 1925 (post card), Sept. 27, 1928, Feb. 13, 1929, Apr. 7, 1933, Jan. 23, 1935, Oct. 1, 1945, Oct. 4, 1945, Nov. 5, 1945, Jan. 1, 1946, Feb. 20, 1946, Mar. 6, 1946, June 9, 1946, June 24, 1946, July 12, 1946; July 16, 1946 (telegram), July 18, 1946, Aug. 29, 1946, Nov. 29, 1946, Nov. 17, 1949, Jan. 23, 1950 (post card), Oct. 22, 1952 (post card), Aug. 13, 1958 (post card); Aug. 21, 1958 (post card), Nov. 5, 1959, Dec. 4, 1959, Mar. 21, 1960, Oct. 6, Oct. 18 (Box 11)
  - Payton, T.W. (1), (n.d.) (Box 11)
  - Peacher, Ethelyne Moore (1), Dec. 28, 1944 (Box 11)
  - Peachy, Joseph C. (1), Jan. 18, 1947 (Box 11)
  - Pearson, Guyla (1), Jan. 27, 1949 (post card) (Box 11)
  - Pearson, Tyson A. (2), June 12, 1956, July 13, 1956 (Box 11)
  - Pearson, William N. (1), Nov. 21, 1951 (Box 11)
  - Pedrick, C. Jr. (1), Mar. 2, 1950 (Box 11)
  - Peebles, Grace Jackson (1), Apr. 18, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Peeler, E.N. (2), Nov. 5, 1957, Nov. 5, 1957 (Box 11)
  - Pegler, Westbrook (4), Feb. 2, 1949, Sept. 22, 1949, Feb. 2, 1950, Feb. 14 (Box 11)
  - Pennell, J.O. Jr. (1), Jan. 29, 1947 (Box 11)
  - Pennoyer, Mrs. C.T. (1), Dec. 5, 1933 (Box 11)
  - Perez, Leander H. (1), Aug. 26, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Perkins, James W. (6), Aug. 11, 1959, Oct. 27, 1960, Sept. 8, 1961, July 25, 1962, Mar. 2, 1965, (n.d.) (Box 11)
  - Perry, Harry A. (1), June 12, 1944 (Box 11)
  - Parry, Mrs. Harry A. (1), June 16, 1948 (telegram) (Box 11)
  - Perry, Winifred Johnston (1), Dec. 11, 1942 (Box 11)
  - Perryman, Esta R. (1), Feb. 28, 1945 (Box 11)
  - Petersen, Peter (1), Sept. 2, 1928 (Box 11)
  - Peterson, C.E. (1), Sept. 30, 1949 (Box 11)
  - Peterson, Don H. (1), Sept. 7, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Peterson, Haydon (1), Oct. 24, 1952 (Box 11)
  - Peterson, Joseph (1), Mar. 22, 1935 (post card) (Box 11)
  - Pettengill, Samuel B. (1), Mar. 10, 1944 (to Mr. Lehr) (Box 11)
  - Pettit, Mrs. H.F. (2), Mar.2, 1944, June 23, 1944 (Box 11)
  - Peyman, D.A.R. (1), Dec. 7, 1950 (post card) (Box 11)
  - Pharr, Clyde (5), July 13, 1951, Aug. 22, 1952, Nov. 8, 1952, Jan. 21, 1954, Sept. 5, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Phi Beta Kappa (2), June 5, 1945 (post card), (n.d.) (Box 11)
  - Phillips, C.Spencer (1), June 17, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Phillips, Ethan V. (1), Jan. 26, 1946 (Box 11)
  - Phillips, Herbert J. (2), Sept. 23, 1949, May 19, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Phillips, James M. (1), Nov. 18, 1943 (Box 11)
  - Phillirn, M. (1), Dec. 30, 1952 (Box 11)
  - Pickering, Sam (2), Feb. 1, 1955, July 23, 1957 (Box 11)
  - Pierson, John B. (1), May 17, 1948 (Box 11)
  - Pioneers of Tennessee (1), Aug. 11, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Piper, Otto A. (1), Jan. 25, 1946 (Box 11)
  - Pittman, R. Carter (1), Sept. 14, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Pitts, C.L. (1), Sept. 14, 1945 (Box 11)
  - Playter, Harold (1), July 16, 1936 (Box 11)
  - Pledger, Charles E.Jr. (1), Hay 15, 1935 (Box 11)
  - Porter, Barbara (1), Aug. 9, 1952 (Box 11)
  - Poteat, H.M. (1), Sept. 21, 1927 (Box 11)
  - Poteat, William H. (1), Mar. 7, 1956 (Box 11)
  - Potter, Justin (1), Sept. 12, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Pouch, William H. (1), June 29, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Pounders, J.J. (1), Dec. 4, 1945 (Box 11)
  - Pouw-Neumann, G. (11), Mar. 3, 1938, Aug. 31, 1945, June 21, 1949, Aug. 10, 1949, Aug. 21, 1949, Dec. 9, 1949, Feb. 1, 1950, Mar. 10, 1950, May 29, 1950, July 20, 1950, Jan. 18, 1951 (Box 11)
  - Powell, E.J. (1), June 20, 1935 (Box 11)
  - Prasse, Freeman (1), Oct. 14, 1946 (Box 11)
  - Pratt, Arthur Peabody (3), Apr. 5, 1944, Feb. 6, 1945, Nov. 30, 1951 (Box 11)
  - Pratt, Helen Armstrong (1), Nov. 15, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Pratt, J.H. (1), June 15, 1950 (post card) (Box 11)
  - Pratt, Norman T.Jr. (1), Jan. 15, 1959 (Box 11)
  - Prentice, E. Parmalee (1), Sept. 7, 1944 (Box 11)
  - Price, Don K. (1), Apr. 9, 1957 (Box 11)
  - Prince, Mr.and Mrs. S. Hardy (1), Feb. 10, 1949 (Box 11)
  - Prince, Tommy (1), Mar. 29, 1961 (Box 11)
  - Probasco, Abbie (1), Mar. 10, 1945 (to John H. Melzer) (Box 11)
  - Provine, Katharine Le ciueur (1), Oct. 8, 1952 (Box 11)
  - Provine, Robert Calhoun (2), June 4, 1927, Oct. 8, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Provine, William K. (1), Oct. 8, 1952 (to President Carmichael) (Box 11)
  - Putman, Russell L. (1), Apr. 1, 1944 (Box 11)
  - Putman, Harold L. (1), June 14, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Putnam, Herbert (1), Jan. 8, 1908 (post card) (Box 11)
  - Puzzanghera, Edith (5), Dec. 20, 1944, Dec. 30, 1944, Jan. 11, 1945, Jan. 10, 1958, Dec. 11, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Pylant, Arch (1), June 11, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Qualls, H.W. (1), (n.d.) (Box 12)
  - Quebbeman, Adam (5), Dec. 5, 1950, Dec. 19, 1950 (post card), June 18, 1951, June 29, 1951, Aug. 3, 1951 (Box 12)
  - Raab, Adam (1), Jan. 2, 1950 (Box 12)
  - Ragan, W.D. (1), July 31, 1934 (Box 12)
  - Ragland, Patricia (1), June 8, 1954 (Box 12)
  - Rainach, W.M. (1), Apr. 10, 1959 (Box 12)
  - Rainbow Terrace (1), (n.d.) (Box 12)
  - Ransom, John Crowe (3), Oct. 19, 1952, Jan. 20, 1959, Oct. 16, 1959 (Box 12)
  - Ransom, W.K. (2), Sept. 21, 1945, Sept. 25, 1945 (Box 12)
  - Rine, Josephine Z. (33), Feb. 6, 1948, Feb. 22, 1950, Mar. 23, 1950 (post card), Apr. 9, 1950 (post card), Nov. 4, 1950, Nov. 24, 1950, Feb. 8, 1951, Feb. 16, 1951, Apr. 5, 1951, May 20, 1951, June 16, 1951, July 22, 1951; Aug. 2, 1951, Aug. 10, 1951, Sept. 27, 1951 (post card), Oct. 7, 1951, Mar. 7, 1952, May 2, 1952, Hay 15, 1952, Aug. 31, 1952, Dec. 27, 1952, Mar. 5, 1953, Feb. 11, 1954, May 20, 1954, June 24, 1954, Aug. 4, 1954, Aug. 22, 1954; Sept. 3, 1954, Sept. 9, 1954, Sept. 16, 1954 (post card), Dec. 23, 1954, Jan. 7, 1955, (n.d.) (Box 12)
  - Rives, Al G. (2), Apr. 22, 1953, Aug. 12, 1957 (Box 12)